(muffled breathing)
(beeps)
(all beeping)
(♪ adventurous music playing)
(birds squawking)
(wailing sound plays)
(♪ enchanting music playing)
Star.
Comm… Command.
Command.
(all) Star. Command.
- Rendezvous!
- With!
(all) Star Command.
Rendezvous with Star Command.
There.
This way, you'll never lose me, Jessie.
Friends forever, partner.
(giggles)
That's right, partner.
But don't you worry.
I'll keep a good eye on you.
(grunts)
See? I'm still watching.
(giggles)
I'm gone… (gasps) …but I'm back.
I'm gone. (gasps) I'm back.
I still see you.
(gasps) Oh, no. (echoing) I'm gone.
And I will love you all the time…
even when I'm mad or sad
or leave you outside by accident.
I'll still love you forever.
(as Jessie) Really? You mean it?
Forever and ever and ever?
Yep. All the evers.
Then do you, Forky, take Karen Beverly
to be your beloved bride?
(as Forky) I do.
And do you, Karen Beverly?
(as Karen Beverly) I do.
(sobs, blows nose)
(giggles)
Yeehaw!
I now pronounce you husband…
and knife.
(kissing)
Kissy, kissy.
- (kissing continues)
- (gasps)
(chuckles)
(gasps) Who poisoned the maid of honor?
(shouts, groans)
- (shouts)
- (all gasp)
- (gasps)
- (screaming)
Oh! Why? Why?
Everyone!
Step aside. I know CPR.
One, two, three.
Now, the kiss of life.
(gasps)
(inhales deeply, blows)
Oh.
- (inhales deeply)
- (car approaching)
(child 1 chuckling)
(child 2) You're so funny.
But we didn't solve my murder.
Just hold your horses, Rex.
Psst. Dolly, what's going on?
(sighs) Not sure.
You know, at first I was mad
Bonnie drew these glasses on me,
but honestly, I can see
so much better now.
Dolly, focus.
Oh! Sorry.
It's the Jordan twins. They're back home.
(twins chattering)
(laughing)
Poor thing. She's still afraid
to ask them to play.
Not this time. (grunts)
(chattering continues)
(Jessie grunts)
Giddy-up there! Time's a-wastin'!
(gasps) Oh, no.
(twins laughing)
That's it, Bonnie.
You can do it.
(Bonnie gasps)
(as Jessie) Hello.
(twins laugh)
(door closes)
Uh, Jessie. The wedding got me thinking…
Shh. Something's off.
So, how'd the wedding go?
Who murdered the maid of honor this time?
Mom? Dad?
Yeah, sweetie?
Why won't anyone be my friend?
(all gasp)
- Oh, Bonnie, come here.
- Oh, sweetie.
- Buzz.
- Ow.
You're deputy till I get back.
Me? Right.
I'm gonna get those twins
to play with Bonnie somehow.
Come on, Bullseye.
(♪ adventurous music playing)
(♪ ominous music playing)
Huh?
Why, they're… they're both
just sitting there.
Doin' nothing.
They ain't playing with toys at all.
What, you didn't hear?
Uh, n-no, I… I didn't hear.
- She didn't hear.
- She didn't hear?
What? What didn't I hear?
The age of toys is over, lass.
What do you mean, "over"?
When did that happen?
It's been happening for years.
Where have you been?
(stammers) Across the street, playing.
(all) Playing?
Oh! Your kid still plays?
I don't remember play. Describe it to me.
(stammers) Are you guys okay?
What happened to you?
- (all) Tech!
- Devices!
Everywhere, devices!
Phones! Tablets!
Computers! Cameras!
The screens just took over!
All the tapping. The tapping!
Tap, tap, tap, tap.
- Make it stop.
- The tapping. Not the tapping!
Take our advice, darlin'.
Find a drawer and hide,
'cause once tech invades your home,
you're dead where you lie.
(chuckles) Oh, well,
it's probably just a fad.
Like, you know, record players
or Hula-Hoops.
You don't get it.
The age of toys is over.
Over.
Tap, tap, tap…
Don't believe us? Come see for yourself.
(Jessie groaning, grunting)
- (grunts, gasps)
- (grunts)
(Jessie) Look at 'em all.
All on devices.
Except for Bonnie.
(sighs)
No wonder she can't
make a friend, Bullseye.
She's the only one out there
still playing with toys.
(sighs)
- Don't worry. We're safe.
- (giggles)
Are we sure about this?
(sighs) No, but I think it might help.
(sighs) Okay.
(phone chimes)
(gasps)
A Lilypad! Oh, thank you, Mom.
Thank you, Dad.
Well, now that you're eight,
we thought you were ready.
Hi, there. I'm Lilypad.
Welcome to The Pond.
You can take today
to figure out how to use it,
but then tomorrow, we'll start having
- strict screen time.
- (Bonnie) Uh-huh.
(Bullseye grunts)
(Lilypad beeping)
(chuckles) Uh-oh, try again.
Keep hopping.
(frog croaking)
(beeping continues)
Try again.
Morning. Screen time's over now.
Let's put Lilypad away
and come to breakfast.
Okay.
(Hamm) We can't let that thing replace us.
Jumpin' jelly beans!
Will y'all just settle down?
Now, I'm gonna have some words
with this Lilypad
and let her know how
things are run around here.
- Try to stay calm, Jessie.
- Buzz, you know me.
I'm the definition of calm.
- (whinnies)
- (Buzz laughs)
That's not gonna work.
(grunts)
(Bullseye grunts)
- Hi!
- What the--
Sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
Sleep mode, you know?
No? Eh, forget it.
I was just gonna hop on the charger.
Battery could use a little refresh.
- I wanna talk to you, device.
- Please, call me "Lily."
Now look here. Me and the toys
have been working all summer
to try and get Bonnie to make
friends with the Jordan twins
- across the street.
- Uh-huh. Yeah.
- Then you had to ruin it…
- Got it.
…with all your stupid…
You're not even listening
- to me!
- Oh, no.
I was listening.
I'm always listening. See?
Now look here. Me and the toys
have been working all summer
to try to get Bonnie to make
friends with the Jordan twins.
Now in Spanish.
- (speaking Spanish)
- (all gasp)
- Now as a rap.
- (♪ drumbeat playing)
♪ Me and the toys
Been working all summer ♪
♪ Trying to get Bonnie
To make friends ♪
Ooh! Our first dance, honey!
Oh, this concerns me ethically.
(♪ drumbeat stops)
Whatever. You don't understand.
Our kid needs to learn
how to make friends,
and your screen ain't helping.
Look, if it's friends Bonnie needs,
consider it done.
- (chimes)
- There.
What? (stammers) What happened?
Oh, it was easy. I just
sent a friend request
to all the girls in Bonnie's dance class.
But that's… They're not here.
Oh, yes, they are, silly.
Chelsea, Kara and even Heidi,
they're all here.
The parents created
a group chat on The Pond.
You see, on The Pond,
while Bonnie's playing
my fun learning games,
she can also socialize with other kids.
That's why Mom and Dad bought
me. To make connections.
- Voilà! Friend made.
- (all exclaim)
I want one.
That Lilypad made Bonnie
a friend in, like…
Fifteen seconds. I was counting.
- What? No.
- No touching.
That ain't a friend. A real
friend would actually be here.
Well, that's my point, Jessica.
(gasps)
- Oh, no.
- (Hamm) She used the "J" word.
(Rex) Scandal!
With my help, eventually Bonnie can reach
all of her developmental goals.
I just want what's best for her.
I think I know more
than a green calculator
what's best for Bonnie.
- Uh, really?
- Yeah, really.
I got three kids' worth of know-how.
Bonnie. Before that, Andy,
and before that, Emily.
I think that just means you're old.
Yikes! Wow. Really old.
Fine. We'll wrestle for her.
- Hi-yah! Come on!
- Whoa! (chuckling)
Wrestle me, you frog-faced faker.
That kinda tickles.
- I'll knock ya off this bed.
- I thought we were
- staying calm-- Ah!
- Put up a fight, you riffraff.
- Whoa!
- I'll show you who's better
- for Bonnie.
- Okay.
Nobody said anything about lifting.
- (Dad) Bonnie?
- (Bonnie) Just a sec.
- (Bonnie screams)
- (coughs)
- Mom! Dad!
- Bonnie?
What? (stammers) What's wrong?
Chelsea from dance class
invited me to a sleepover this weekend.
Can I go? Can I go? Can I go?
Please!
Well, uh, all right.
As long as we talk to Chelsea's parents,
I guess it's okay.
Yay! Yes!
(Dad) Come on, everybody. Let's eat.
Yeah, I got dibs on behind the dresser.
Should buy me a few years.
Ah! Extinction. Not again.
- Called it.
- Don't get me started.
Now, look. Our time ain't over yet.
Bonnie still loves us.
- (Dolly) Really?
- (Jessie) She does.
Sure. Whatever you say, Sheriff.
It's just a phase.
(sighs)
(♪ sentimental music playing)
(♪ marching music playing)
(static crackling)
(sighs)
(beeping)
'Ello? Caboom here. Over.
- (Jessie) Oh! Duke.
- Hey there, Red.
- Long time.
- Hey. Um…
- Is Woody there?
- Please hold.
(exclaims) Hey, cowboy!
Pump the brakes, Duke, he's mid-rescue.
Bad squirrel! No! Yeah, bad!
- Evil squirrel! No!
- Okay, now, Mr. Nutcase.
- Doctor. Doctor.
- Okay, Dr. Nutcase.
On three, you're going to unstick yourself
- and drop into my arms.
- (sobbing)
What's the point? It's over for toys.
The screens have won, and now
the squirrel's gonna eat me!
You guys ready?
Just one text, ping,
and Trevor totally forgot
I was stuck in the tree.
(crying) We're doomed!
Okay, one, two…
I give up!
(shouts) Three, three!
I got you. I got you.
(Dr. Nutcase sobbing)
- Okay. It's okay. I got you.
- Let me go! I'm yucky.
- (Woody) Hello, Jessie? Hello?
- (gasps) Woody!
Jessie, hey. What's going on?
- Curse technology!
- Hey, quiet down.
(Dr. Nutcase) We're all just landfill now.
Woody, is it as bad out there
for toys as they say it is?
- Beware the machines!
- Just let go!
Yeah. Yeah, it's bad.
We're finding
more abandoned toys each day.
Why? Are you guys okay?
Not really. Tech's invaded our house too.
(Woody) Oh, no.
Yeah, her name's Lilypad.
Looks like a frog,
but really, she's a leech,
sucking up all of Bonnie's attention.
Making her stare at her screen all day.
There's got to be some way to stop it.
(stammers) I don't know, Jessie. Uh…
Toys are for play, but tech is…
it's for everything.
(sighs)
You remember my first kid, Emily?
The one I told you about who gave me away.
(Woody) Course I do, yeah.
It feels like that all over again.
First we were playing…
(Emily laughs)
…and then the world started changing.
(laughs) I know.
(Jessie) Emily changed and then…
just like that…
my time with her was over.
Now I'm losing Bonnie to this device.
Is it me?
Am I just no good at being a toy?
(Woody) Jessie, you're a good toy.
- I don't know.
- (Woody) Jessie.
(Bullseye grunts)
(inhales sharply) Okay.
Jessie… (clears throat)
No, Sheriff… Sheriff Jessie,
I appreciate this promotion,
but what I'd really like to promote…
No, that is so stupid.
(Bullseye sniffing)
But she got Bonnie invited
to a sleepover in seconds.
(Woody) Jessie, you know
Bonnie better than anyone.
What does your gut say?
- That it can't be that easy.
- (Woody) Mm-hmm.
Bonnie won't click
- with just anyone.
- Exactly.
She needs to actually meet these girls.
She's not like most kids.
Bonnie plays different. She…
She needs to play.
- (Woody) Jessie?
- You're right, Woody.
Toys are for play.
And play is how
she'll find the right friend.
Okay.
The age of toys may be over,
but I'm gonna do something
useful before I go.
I'm going to that sleepover,
and making a real friend for Bonnie.
- Jessie, are you okay?
- (gasps) Buzz!
- Jessie? Jessie!
- (static on radio)
What do you think you're doing?
What are you doing?
I assumed you needed backup.
No! I don't…
Need backup, Deputy.
(gasps)
- (whispers) What happened?
- Why are we whispering?
- He's finally asleep.
- (snoring)
So what's wrong?
I don't know, but you heard Jessie.
She needs a deputy.
(screams) Machines!
- Jessie.
- Yeah, what is it?
Uh…
(stammers) You know…
Never mind. Never mind.
If you need anything,
I'm here. At your service.
Okay. Thanks.
Come on, Bullseye.
I'm gonna need your help.
(Bullseye whinnies)
(Buzz sighs)
(♪ adventurous music playing)
We can't see the stars, Buzz.
Too much fog.
Hmm. We need to find higher ground.
- (gasps)
- (all beeping)
(♪ dramatic music playing)
(machinery whirring)
Huh?
A-ha!
Buzz, I have our bearings.
East-north-- (gasps)
I'm not cleaning that up.
- Why did we…
- Freeze?
(all) Fascinating.
- Must…
- Avoid…
Humans.
(all) Affirmative.
(♪ dramatic music plays)
(music fades)
Bonnie! Time to go to your sleepover.
Hmm.
Um…
Yo, Bonnie, uh, what are you doing?
You said you finished packing.
Well, I did, but it's
my very first sleepover, Dad.
I wanna be extra, extra prepared.
You're gonna be fine, sweetie.
Come on. Go put on your shoes.
We got to go.
Okay, okay.
(clears throat)
Jessie. (gasps)
(Lilypad) Uh…
What are you doing?
We are gonna check out
these "friends" for ourselves
and see if there is a real one
in the bunch.
Okay, pause. It is not
a good look for Bonnie
- to bring toys to a sleepover.
- (scoffs)
- I do. I do. I do.
- Deputy Buzz.
I do! I mean, I've done things.
Make sure that device
don't take charge of anything
while we're away.
Yes, Sheriff. I'm on it.
- (Dad) All right, time to go.
- (Bonnie) Okay.
No, Jessie. Get out of that bag.
I'm only thinking about
what's best for Bonnie.
Well, what do you know?
That's exactly what I'm doing.
- (door closes)
- (car rumbling)
(Dad) Did you pack your toothbrush?
- (Bonnie) I think so.
- (zipper opens)
Oh, thanks, Dad. You packed
Jessie and Bullseye.
Uh, did I? Well, you're welcome.
(Bonnie sighs)
- And here we are.
- (gasps)
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
I wonder if Kara and Heidi are here yet.
Oh! Over there. Dad,
I see them. Park right there.
(Dad) Okay, okay. I see them.
Uh, Bonnie. You forgot your bag.
(panting)
- Hey, Chelsea.
- Oh, hey, Bonnie.
- Guys, you remember Bonnie?
- Hi.
And this is Jessie.
(as Jessie) I ain't afraid
of nothin', partner.
Oh. You still play with toys?
(friends laughing)
(Bonnie gasps)
Um… Uh…
Uh, um… uh…
No. Be right back.
- Here you go, sweetie.
- Dad, take these.
But I thought you wanted your toys?
Dad, just go.
(♪ ominous music plays)
(gasps)
Guys,
- I got my Lilypad.
- Bye!
- (gasps)
- (Bonnie groans)
No.
(Bonnie grunts)
(grunts)
(panting)
(groans)
(grunts)
(gasps)
No, no, no.
No, no, no, this is all wrong.
How is she supposed to make friends
if they ain't even looking at each oth--
(screams)
Oh.
- (gasps)
- (footsteps approaching)
Oh, no. Somebody lost their toys.
What's that?
I said somebody lost their toys.
Let's see.
(gasps)
They belong to an Emily.
(driver) Oh, and there's an address.
- That's not too far from here.
- (gasps)
We can drop them off.
(phone) Turn right onto Ranch Road.
(phone) You've reached your destination.
(grunting)
I'll just leave them here in the mailbox.
What's that?
I'm leaving them in the mailbox.
- You're leaving me?
- Yes.
(panting) No, no, no.
No, no, no.
No! (panting)
We cannot be here.
We've gotta get back to Bonnie!
Come on, Bullseye. (grunts)
(♪ adventurous music playing)
(Jessie panting)
(exclaims, grunts)
(♪ ominous music playing)
- (gasps)
- (grunts)
(thuds)
- (snorts)
- (Jessie shouts)
(screams)
Uh-oh! Uh! Oh!
(chuckling) Whoa!
Whoo!
(laughing)
Hi!
Bullseye! You thinking what I'm thinking?
Yeah! Yeah, I'm gonna speak critter,
and we'll ride this horse home!
We're coming, Bonnie!
Yeehaw!
- (whinnies)
- (Jessie shouts)
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Wrong way, horsey!
Wrong way!
- (whinnies)
- Whoa, horsey! Whoa!
No! No, no, no, no!
- Whoa!
- (thudding)
(Jessie coughing)
(groans)
(coughs, groans)
(sighs)
Bullseye?
(horse whinnies, snorts)
(Jessie) Oh!
Thank goodness. Come here. Help me.
(person) Daffodil?
Geez, are you all right?
- (gasps)
- Did something spook you?
Come on, girl. (clicks tongue)
Come on. Good girl.
Hmm?
(gasps)
Where'd you come from?
(chuckling) He's perfect.
No. Bullseye.
Mmm… Hmm.
Hmm.
And how exactly will this help
us get Bonnie's attention?
Well, when they come back
from the sleepover…
- Careful. That tickles.
- …she'll enter the room,
see Forky and Karen Beverly,
and remember the wedding.
We are talking about Bonnie, right?
And not Jessie?
Huh? (chuckles)
Of course Bonnie. (chuckles) Just Bonnie.
Hey, what's everyone talking about?
Buzz is gonna propose to Jessie.
- Propose?
- (Trixie) Finally.
Wait a minute. Wait…
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
(stammers) I didn't say that.
- You didn't not say it either.
- Well, I…
Who, Buzz?
Question. Is Woody gonna
perform the wedding ceremony?
I haven't thought
that far in advance, Forky.
Okay. Then why is Woody at the window?
(all gasp) Woody!
Woody!
- Hey, everybody!
- (all) Bo!
Howdy, folks. Coast clear?
The stage is yours, my friend.
(all) Woody!
- It's good to s…
- Wow.
(♪ Western guitar plays)
Pretty cowboy.
Why are you wearing a dress, Woody?
It's called a poncho, Forky.
Thought I'd change it up.
Yeah?
Well, Bo likes it.
(sighs) It's good to be back.
- Shiny.
- What?
- (all) Nothing.
- Love the poncho.
Someone needs a brown marker.
Wow. Look what Bonnie's done
with the place.
(chuckling) It's…
She really let things go.
- Oh, my.
- Oh.
I see Sammy got bigger.
- Uh, that's Sammy number two.
- No.
- (all) Yeah.
- I'll explain it.
There was a Sammy number one,
and then he died.
- Poor Samuel.
- (beeping)
- Halt. Who goes there?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sor… Sorry. My name is Woody.
I come in peace. Used to live here.
All right.
(chuckles)
It's been too long, cowboy.
- How've you been?
- Ah, busy.
Came here as fast as I could
after Jessie called for help.
- Good thing we were in town.
- She called you?
- Yeah, I'm her deputy.
- But I'm her deputy.
- Uh…
- (chuckles)
- That's odd.
- (chuckling) Well, well…
there must be a little mix-up here.
- Well, no offense, Woody.
- Oh, none taken. None taken.
But she literally
- deputized me.
- Oh, is that so?
- Woody, look. Eyes here.
- Uh-huh.
- Star. Deputy. Me.
- No star.
- (stammers) I got you.
Star. No star.
- Oh, hey, Buzz, what is that?
- What? Where?
Ow.
- Hey. Wait…
- What?
Just happy to help, Deputy.
(sighs) Call me when
you're done helping, dear.
(Woody) Thanks, Bo.
(Duke) Okay, ladies.
- (Bo) Girls weekend!
- Yes.
Un, deux, trois!
(horn beeps)
Where is Jessie, anyway?
Sleepover reconnaissance.
Yeah, she and Bullseye are
helping Bonnie make friends.
While fending off the nefarious Lilypad.
It's Dolly, by the way. Glasses.
Didn't you always have glasses?
What? No.
We've got it handled, cowboy.
As her deputy, I'm certain
Jessie's resting
on a comfy pillow right now
making all the difference for Bonnie.
(Jessie groaning, straining)
(groaning continues)
(sighs)
(whinnies)
(scoffs) You're no help.
(gasps)
Hey, you can help get me out of here.
(summons Daffodil)
Come here. Come on. Come on. Daffodil.
Yeah, yeah, come over here.
Come on. Come on.
(gasps)
- (snorts)
- (chuckles)
Nice pig. Nice pig.
Stinky pig.
- (screams)
- (grunts)
Hey, hey, there.
(stammers) I guess you'll have to do.
Jimmy Dean?
You mean, like, the… Oh, no.
- (squeals)
- Oh!
- Okay. Wow, that's your name?
- (grunting)
Jimmy Dean?
Take me to the house.
- (squealing)
- (gasps)
Golly gee whillikers! It's working.
(exclaiming)
Hey! Ugh! Yuck!
(gasping) Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yes!
Yes. Yes, good pig. Good pig. Good--
No. No, no, no.
Bad pig. Oh, wrong way, Jimmy.
Oh, no, no. Wrong house, Jimmy.
Wrong house. Wrong-- (grunts)
(Jimmy grunting)
No. (grunts)
(panting, strains)
- (Combat Carl) Blaze?
- (gasps)
(all groan)
False alarm, everyone.
Um…
Oh, apologies. Where are
Combat Carl's manners?
(stammers) Welcome. Please, take a seat.
Oh. (chuckles)
No. I've gotta get home.
- No, no! Sit.
- Please, sit.
- (speaks Spanish)
- Combat Carl insists.
Oh. Okay.
- (all clamoring)
- No, no, no!
- Oh, sorry. I'm sorry.
- Any chair but that one.
Who… Who sits there?
(all) Blaze.
Blaze. You mean the girl I saw
in the barn?
She's your kid?
(sighs) Isn't she swell?
She loves her tea parties.
And telling us all her secrets.
That's right, Pizza With Sunglasses.
To Blaze's return.
(all) To Blaze's return!
(sipping)
Mmm. Rico.
Ooh, hot.
(smacks lips) Uh…
How long has it been
since your Blaze last had tea?
Things were never really the same
- once he arrived.
- He?
Smarty Pants. Blaze's first device.
- You're sitting on him.
- What?
(gasps) Holy butterscotch!
(beeps)
(♪ playing music)
Why, hello there. Pick a number.
- Not again!
- Make it stop! Don't!
- Oh, just kill me.
- Come on.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
- Hey, hey!
- No! Don't!
This… This isn't the bathroom.
How long have I been off?
- Shut up, chair!
- We hate you.
Turn him off.
(groans) Gosh.
Who's this little, old, tiny grandma lady?
- Gosh, what is wrong with him?
- Low batteries.
(Smarty Pants groaning)
Eggman?
(groans) You're one of those Pond devices.
- (burps)
- (groans)
I already have to put up with
a Lilypad back home.
- Hey.
- I don't have time for this.
(grunting) Your Blaze took my
horse into the house…
and we gotta get back to our own kid.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're going inside?
- Take me with you, please!
- Not a chance.
You need help pushing?
I'm… (hiccups) …great with pushing.
You can do it. You can do it.
Like a choo-choo,
- you can poop.
- No!
How about you just wait here
with your friends?
Spend another second with
Corporal No-Pants? (hiccups)
I'm coming with you, cowgirl.
No way. Your kind's caused me
enough trouble.
My kind?
- Take him!
- Please! Get him out of here!
All he's good for is chair.
I am not a chair!
I am a potty trainer!
Show some respect!
Okay, listen, Raggedy Ann.
All these losers are outdoor toys.
I'm the only one who's
done time inside. (hiccups)
You wanna find your horsey? Clippity-clop.
I know exactly where Blaze put him, okay?
You need me. You need me. You need me.
Hi.
(Jessie) Move. Move.
(all grunt)
Hey, geez. Someone dim
the brightness out here.
- Shut up.
- Would you try walking
- a little less bouncy?
- Shut up.
Quick. Lock the door before
they change their minds.
Copy that.
(♪ marching music playing)
(gasps) Halt.
(wailing sound playing)
(sniffing)
(wailing stops)
- (sniffs)
- (chuckles)
♪ Love is a song
That never ends ♪
(Buzzes chuckle)
♪ Life may be swift
And fleeting ♪
(all chuckling)
♪ Hope may die
Yet love's beautiful music ♪
♪ Comes each day
Like the dawn-- ♪
(♪ ominous music playing)
Hon, I'm pretty sure we go this way.
(spouse) You sure?
(grunting)
(footsteps approaching)
Save yourselves.
It's this line here.
If we follow it…
- There's our camp.
- Oh, I see.
Yeah, that looks right.
Hey, wait for me, guys!
- Whoa. No way.
- (all gasp)
Hey, Morgan! Look at this.
(Morgan) Lucky. Hey, let me see it.
Nope. Finders keepers.
- Mom!
- Man down.
- Code red.
- Code red. Code red. Code red.
- Kids, be nice.
Code red. Code red. Code red.
Blaze, I'm going out. Be back in an hour.
(Blaze) Okay, Mom.
(grunts, panting)
Get Bullseye, get out.
- Hey, cowgirl?
- Shh.
- (gasps)
- Ooh. Forgot my keys.
(Jessie gasps, exclaims)
- Ugh! (coughing)
- (Smarty Pants groaning)
Really don't feel so good.
I think I'm gonna… (burps) …reboot.
(♪ upbeat music playing)
Shh. Quiet, quiet, quiet.
Quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet.
- (grunts) Quiet.
- (♪ music stops)
(gasps)
(Smarty Pants) Wait. Wait.
Wait, I'm back.
I'm back home.
- This is where it all started.
- (groans)
Yeah.
- It's all changed.
- (groans)
(gasps) Smarty, no.
I-I have to find Bullseye. Wake up!
- Need more juice.
- (beeping)
Okay! W-Where are the batteries?
Where do I find the batteries?
Bottom drawer, next to the stamps.
(strains)
Why, hello there! Pick a number.
Is it number one?
- Whoa! I feel great!
- Shh!
- Look at me!
- Shh! No!
- Yes! (laughs)
- No, we're not doing this now.
- Not now.
- I am back!
- Cut it out!
- (gasps)
Snappy. Atlas. They're still here!
Oh! Bossy cowgirl,
we have to turn 'em back on.
No! No way.
The last thing this world
needs is more devices.
What, what, what?
You're just gonna shove 'em
back in the dark forever?
Do you have any idea what that's like?
(♪ pensive music playing)
(sighs)
Fine. We gotta make this quick.
(laughs) Yes!
Number one! You made number--
- Atlas! Snappy!
- Smarty!
- Smarty? Is that you?
- Is it really you?
- It's really me! Yes!
- My goodness. You look great.
- The AA-Team is back!
- Oh, my gosh. Yes!
Mom brought us inside
after that tantrum Blaze had,
and we never saw you again.
- So tell me. What did I miss?
- Oh, my gosh.
Well, we've been down a long time too.
But look! I could show you how
first and second grade went!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Please do that. Yeah.
Look at her! She's so much older.
- I know, right?
- She's adorable.
- Isn't she?
- She got bangs that year.
- Wait a minute. Where is that?
- That's Disneyland.
Zoom in. That's me in her pocket.
Oh, flush. You both went there?
- (Snappy) Mm-hmm. For reals.
- (Atlas) It's so beautiful.
And, uh, that's the last of it.
Next, it was just
a spinning rainbow wheel.
Then… darkness.
My entire SD card flashed before my eyes.
- (Smarty Pants) Wow.
- (Atlas) Aw.
Okay, okay. I am glad you're
all powered up and stuff,
but we're wasting time I don't got.
Oh, we're so grateful to you, cowboy lady.
Guys, guys, guys,
this is pushy cowgirl Jessie.
She claims she's a sheriff.
Just go with it.
- Blaze has her horse, Banzai--
- Bullseye!
And I gotta get us back
to our kid, Bonnie, now.
She needs us. So, where is he, Smarty?
All right, okay. I said
I'd tell ya, so I'll tell ya.
- Drumroll please.
- (thudding)
He's probably in the bedroom.
Probably in the bedroom?
I could've guessed that.
- And yet, you did not, Dusty.
- Dusty?
Yeah, you know, like ancient,
elderly, mummified old fart.
Or as I like to call it, number 1.5.
- I missed you, Smarty.
- (chuckles)
You know what?
- I've had enough of your cr--
- Oh, wait!
I just had an idea that could
maybe help you get to Bonnie.
- (sighs) What?
- It's a little technical,
but if the three of us link up--
No, no, I am done
with this techno mumbo jumbo.
No offense, but I'll be fine
getting back on my own.
Offense taken!
You're muted, Dave. You're muted.
Okay. There you go.
(Dave) Only have a bit
of time left. One more time--
(Blaze's dad) You're muted again, Dave.
(Smarty Pants grunting)
Oh, cheese and crackers!
What are you doing? Get back.
You're not the only one
who misses their kid, okay?
- Now help us up.
- (sighs)
(all grunting)
Careful, careful! You're gonna unplug me.
- (door opens)
- Blaze, I'm home.
(Blaze) Hey, Mom!
Back, back, back!
- (toys grunting)
- Hey, Mom?
- Wait a second. Is that…
- Is that big girl Blaze?
- She's changed so much!
- Like overnight.
- Is she here yet?
- (Blaze's mom) Not yet.
Why don't you try messaging her?
- (Snappy) Whoa.
- She big, big.
- She…
- (toilet flushes)
She did it without me.
- (Snappy) Wow.
- (gasps)
- It's so pretty.
- It's so clean!
(Smarty Pants) When did she become neat?
(Atlas) I can see the floor.
(Snappy) I can see me in the floor.
It smells like vanilla.
With hints of brown sugar.
(Smarty Pants) You know who I don't miss?
(Snappy) That stupid stuffed whale.
- (Atlas) What was his name?
- (Smarty Pants) Spouty.
(Snappy) The worst.
(Smarty Pants) Give me a break.
(Snappy) Annoying.
Seriously, how much have we missed?
Everything.
Your Blaze ain't the kid
you remember anymore.
How would you know?
(sighs) I've seen all this before.
Spent a lot of years under the bed
watching my first kid grow up without me.
- Hey, that's our address.
- (GPS beeping)
How old is Blaze anyway? Nine, ten?
Her room looks like a teenager's.
She's nine and a half,
thank you very much.
It's 'cause you devices
make 'em change so fast.
(groans) I gotta get back.
- So, where--
- (whinnies)
Bullseye! Thank goodness.
Uh-huh, they seem nice, Bullseye,
but we have to go now.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
So you're saying that
this was your room too?
- Yes.
- (scoffs) Really?
- (chuckling)
- What, you calling me a liar?
No…
Yeah. Yeah, liar.
(sighs)
(♪ tense music playing)
There's a knot in the ceiling,
looks like an angry eye
when you squint at it.
Window's got a small crack
like a spider in
the upper right-hand corner.
And out on that tire swing hill,
Emily and I would play
every summer afternoon.
Now, Bullseye, let's go.
Uh, you're welcome.
For what? You didn't help me
at all. You were--
What? Go on. Say it.
- Useless.
- (gasps)
- Oh, no, she didn't.
- Oh, snap!
- (Jimmy Dean snorting)
- (gasps)
Oh, no. Not the pig!
(♪ "I Love It" playing through headphones)
- (Blaze humming)
- (snorting)
Jimmy got big.
Lay it on me, Jimmy Dean!
Who's coming? Sally's coming.
Yeah, yeah. She's coming.
She's coming to my house.
Hey, Mom! Sally's texting me right now.
She's probably on her way.
(♪ melancholy music playing)
(sighs)
(sobbing)
(snorting)
You'll be my friend, right, Jimmy?
Always.
By the way, your hair looks so good today.
(chuckles)
Thank you, Jimmy.
She's perfect!
(blusters)
We gotta get Blaze to meet Bonnie.
(chuckles)
(snoring)
- Bonnie.
- (gasps)
Tag, you're it!
We're home.
Hi, hon. How was the sleepover?
I don't wanna talk about it.
- Why? What happened?
- Nothing.
That doesn't sound good.
I don't see Jessie.
Calm down, lover boy.
Your fiancée's coming.
Fiancée?
Buzz Lightyear, you never told me.
I know. Isn't it exciting?
Well, it's not official yet.
I have to, you know, ask her.
Uh, FYI, I am ordained.
- Since when?
- Last Halloween.
Bonnie made me a haunted priest, remember?
- (toys) Oh, yeah.
- Guys, places.
Bonnie's coming.
(Bonnie's mom) Did you make some friends?
I guess so.
Aw, she looks awful.
Does anyone see Jessie?
(Woody) So, that's Lilypad?
(Bonnie's mom)
How about I make you a snack?
(Bonnie) Yes, please. I'm starving.
Jessie. (grunts) Jessie. Bullseye.
- Where are you?
- Oh, no, oh, no.
Is this not the right version?
What? Where's Jessie? Where's Bullseye?
I'm a little busy
helping Bonnie right now.
What on earth happened at that sleepover?
Excuse me. What are you?
Are you like some sort of old man toy?
What?
She thinks you're old
because you're bald, Woody.
- Why, you little--
- Where's Jessie?
What happened to Bonnie?
She looks miserable.
Uh, the girls may have played
hide-and-seek
and, um, forgotten to find Bonnie.
- (all gasp)
- Poor Bonnie.
How could you let that happen?
I didn't. You toys did this!
These girls have been
on The Pond for over a year,
but Bonnie is behind
because all of the time
she's been playing with you!
I need to bring her up to speed fast,
starting with Turtle Tag.
It's the quickest way for her
to connect with the girls.
I'm only gonna ask one more time, frog.
Where is Jessie?
Not my problem. I'm very busy.
- (all gasp)
- That's it.
- We'll make her talk.
- I'll do it, Woody.
- (grunts)
- Hey! Hey!
- I got it. I'll--
- I got it, Buzz. No.
- (Lilypad) Back off, buddy.
- I got this. Ow!
Do not touch me. Don't touch--
Where's Jessie?
Okay. You toys are out of here.
(♪ ominous music playing)
(gasps) Wait. She's doing something.
- So long, toys.
- (alarm blaring)
(shouts)
- Turn her off!
I can't! I can't! It's not responding!
I have plastic fingers!
She's coming.
(alarm stops)
You sure you want me to take these toys?
Mm-hmm.
Okay. It's your room.
(gasps)
No!
They'll be in the garage if you want them.
Yep.
(Mr. Pricklepants) I now
pronounce us in storage.
(chuckles) Playing with you is fun.
Okay. Now what do we d--
(♪ melancholy music playing)
(sighs)
Don't worry, Buzz. We're gonna find her.
I promise.
(sighs)
Woody, I know it's just
a pretend ceremony,
and Bonnie usually
decides these things, but…
Well, if it were up to me,
you'd be my best man.
(gasps)
Buzz, I…
I'd be honored.
(sighs) But Jessie
will never speak to me again
now that I've let Lily
take charge of the room.
Wait a min-- Take charge.
- I tried to.
- No, no, no. Buzz, that's it.
What is?
(♪ suspenseful music playing)
Tomorrow morning,
everyone will wake up fully recharged…
except Lilypad.
And then we'll make Lily
tell us… Where's Jessie?
(Blaze snoring)
Oh, finally.
Psst. Hey.
(Smarty Pants) It's okay. Just ignore her.
- (Atlas) Shh, shh.
- (Snappy) Quiet!
(Smarty Pants) Nobody's home.
- I can hear you.
- (Snappy) Smarty!
- What? I used a faraway voice.
- (Atlas) Come on, man!
- Look. Camera--
- It's Snappy.
Right, Snappy.
You said there was a way you could help us
get to Bonnie, right? So, what is it?
(Smarty Pants)
She did say that, didn't she?
That sounds, I don't know…
- (Snappy) Useful?
- That's it, yeah.
Too bad we're useless!
- (Snappy) Right!
- (Atlas) Yeah! Remember?
- (blusters)
- (sighs)
I'm sorry I called you useless.
You three are definitely of use…
somehow.
- (Snappy) Worst apology ever.
- (Atlas) Just awful.
(Smarty Pants) Now I want
an apology for that apology.
(sighs)
Please. I know I messed up.
I was wrong about your kid, Blaze.
She's creative and silly
in a way other kids don't really get.
(stammers) Am I right?
Go on.
Well, our kid's like that too.
And I think they'd really like each other.
So, fine, if you don't want to help me,
let's just help our kids.
All right, twist my handle.
Yeah! We're making friends.
- F-R-E-N-D.
- With an "I."
(Snappy) F-R-I-N-D.
Great! So, how do we connect them?
You said your kid's device was
on The Pond like me, right?
Right! So Smarty, Atlas and I
are all compatible, see?
And I could take a picture of you.
- Okay, act like a toy.
- O-Okay.
Uh, not very photogenic, are they?
- And Atlas can add text to it.
- Mm-hmm.
- Then we post it on The Pond.
- (Atlas) Yep.
Where Bonnie is!
(all) Ta-da!
- Great! So, you sent it?
- (♪ gentle music playing)
No. Still going.
(sighs)
How about now?
(exclaims) Still going.
Still going? How is that possible?
Look at my eyes! The little
toilet roll's still spinning.
I'm only as fast as my operating system.
So just slow your roll, all right?
- (chimes)
- There. It's sent.
Finally. Now what?
Now, we wait.
Yeah, everyone's still asleep.
We gotta wait for Bonnie
to wake up and see the post.
(groans, sighs)
Hey, I know! We could play a game.
- Yes!
- Yeah!
- A game?
It was Blaze's favorite.
It's called "Pick the Poop."
You try and hit the button
when the poop shows up over it.
Hey, Smarty.
I will never play that game.
(chuckles) They all say that.
(insects chirping)
(child laughing)
(sibling) Come on!
- It's my turn.
- (mom) Okay, you two.
Time to stop playing with your new toy.
- It's bedtime.
- (children groan)
- Already?
- Do we have to?
- (mom) Yeah, come on.
- (children groan)
(♪ tense music playing)
(laptop beeps)
Huh?
(mom) "And they had splendid
games together, in whispers,
when Nana had gone away to her supper
and left the night-light burning
on the mantelpiece.
And when the boy dropped off to sleep,
the rabbit would snuggle down close under
- his little, warm chin…"
- (beeping)
Sir.
"…and dream with the boy's hands
clasped close round him all night."
Hmm.
- (gasp) Star Command.
- Star Command.
(all) Star Command.
- (birds chirping)
- (groans)
(yawns, sighs)
What? No, no, no!
Dad! Dad!
What? What is it?
Lily's not working!
I'm missing Turtle Tag!
Kara, Chelsea and Heidi
play it every morning.
- I can't miss it, Dad!
- It's okay.
I plugged it back in.
We just need to wait for it to charge.
But it's not okay!
I'm gonna miss the game!
Sweetie, there's nothing
we can do for now.
- (Bonnie groans)
- (door closes)
Aha! Success, huh? Look at that.
That's phase one.
- And now, phase two.
- Phase two.
Well, I thought I was gonna
initiate phase two.
I initiate phase two.
We thumb wrestled over this.
All right, fine.
And then we'll have a little talk
with our froggy friend.
- (toy beeping)
- (Blaze snoring)
(grunting)
- One, two, one, two, two…
- I hate this game.
- …one, two, one…
- Please make it stop.
- Mighty Wiper!
- (Atlas shushes)
- Again, again, again!
- I think you need a break.
I can't feel my buttons.
- Just one more time! Come on!
- That's enough play for now.
Play? (scoffs)
That's just a game. That's not playing.
What's the difference?
You know, real play.
You're kidding, right?
You've never seen Blaze play with a toy?
How long were you guys with her?
- Three months.
- Ten months.
- Six months.
- Months?
What? Too long?
Too short! (groans)
Guys, you missed all the fun!
Hey, we're fun.
I mean fun, fun. Make-believe fun.
Just look at her.
Oh, yeah. She plays.
Oh, yeah? Prove it.
Okay, Smarty Pants. We will.
(sniffs, snorting)
(groans)
Morning, Jimmy.
Ready for breakfast? Hmm?
Whoa.
Hey, Mom! Where'd you find the cowgirl?
(chuckles)
I ain't afraid of nothin', partner.
- (chuckles)
- Yeehaw! Let's play!
(gasps)
Yeah.
(chuckles)
Wait a minute.
(Blaze chuckles) Hmm.
Neigh!
Well, flush me.
Blaze is actually gonna play.
(vocalizing) Here we go!
(♪ ballroom music playing)
- M'la-- (gasps)
- (gasps, chuckles)
M'lady Davenport,
I present Her Royal Highness,
Jimmy Queen.
(snorting)
(clears throat)
Your Highness, how kind of you
to invite me to your royal ball--
(babbling)
Jimmy! This is your big moment.
- (snorting)
- (toys beeping)
What you got there, Jimmy?
(snorting)
Whoa.
(chuckling) I can't believe
I still have these.
(gasps) Wait a minute.
(♪ suspenseful music playing)
(Snappy) Agent Clydesdale,
your suitor is approaching now.
(gasps)
So, we meet again, Agent Sheet-land.
It's pronounced Shet-land. "Shet."
That's what I said.
Well, Agent Clydesdale, or should I say,
Lady Davenport, have you spotted it yet?
You mean, the bomb?
Yes! Shh! Quiet!
Snappy, do you have eyes on it?
Not yet. Atlas, do you copy?
Agents! The bomb is right on top of you!
- (beeping)
- (gasps) Where? Where?
(laughs)
Where you never suspected,
Agent Clydesdale!
- (laughing)
- (guests gasping)
- (gasps)
- (laughs)
But where is the bomb?
(beeping)
(exclaims)
She's coming to, Buzz.
(tablet beeping)
Hurry it up.
(Buzz) I'm trying, Woody!
What… What happened?
Wait. What did you do to my battery?
What we'll do again if you don't tell us
what happened to Jessie and Bullseye.
What time is it? (gasps)
Oh, no! This is not good.
The girls got a head start
on Turtle Tag without Bonnie!
There's been one, two,
three inside jokes already.
This is a disaster!
Enough with the silly games.
Where's Jessie and Bullseye?
Silly? This is serious, Stuffalo Bill!
Bonnie is missing out.
Stuffalo Bill?
Want her to make friends? This is how!
Now keep your little
plastic hands away from me
or I will set off my alarm.
I thought you'd say as much.
Buzz, bring in "Sammy Two."
- No. No. Absolutely not.
- (grunting)
- Oh, no, no, no--
- (alarm blaring)
- (Buzz) Yes. (chuckles)
- (alarm stops)
- Okay, try "settings."
- You mean this?
- That's a gear symbol.
- Okay, got it. Now what?
Reduce her screen time to zero.
(Buzz) The shortest is an hour.
- What?
- "Horse grill"? Who is that?
"Horse girl."
- She's talking about Jessie.
- Well, then open it. (gasps)
- Whoa!
- (grunting)
(tablet chimes)
- (Lilypad exclaims)
- (Woody) My hips.
Enjoy the garage, suckers!
- No, no, no! Lily!
- Wait. Hey!
(gasps)
Yes, can I help you?
Huh?
- Wait a minute. (shushes)
- Fascinating.
Lily, bring back that "horse girl" post.
(distorted buzzing)
Okay.
Oh, she has to do what you say.
- (screams)
- (gasps, grunts)
- She's getting away, Buzz!
- Lily!
- Hey, Lily!
- Hey, stop her!
- Yes?
- Open that post!
- Okay!
- (gasps) Jessie.
- Bonnie's gotta see this.
(Buzz) Show her again.
Where is she? Hey, Lily.
- Hey, Lily!
- Yes?
- Show the post.
- Can I help you?
- Share it everywhere!
- Share!
- Yes!
We did it!
So, where did it go?
Lily…
(all grunting)
(Lilypad panting)
- (machine whirring)
- (gasps)
- (Buzz) The printer! Yes!
- (Woody laughs)
(Bonnie) Okay, I'm done.
(Mom) Bonnie, you haven't
finished your breakfast.
- (Bonnie) No, I'm done.
- (gasps)
I'm missing Turtle Tag, Mom.
They're playing without me.
- (groans, pants)
- (Lilypad laughs)
Now what, Deputy?
Well, you're the deputy, Deputy.
What's this all about, Bonnie?
- Huh?
- (groans)
So, why did you put her toys
in the garage?
Uh, because Bonnie asked me to.
- Remember, sweetie?
- No.
(Dad) Well, I don't think
Lilypad texted me.
They're gone. She really does
have Jessie and Bullseye.
I hope they're okay.
Okay, we've gotten the queen to safety.
Yes. You can do this, Agent Clydesdale.
One of these buttons defuses the bomb.
But which one, Agent "Sheetland"?
"Shet"! (sobbing) It's "Shet"!
(beeping)
(beeping stops)
Boom! (imitates explosion)
Oh, no! (imitates explosion) (screams)
(Blaze's mom) Blaze! Hon!
It's time to feed Daffodil.
(kisses) Okay! (chuckles)
Come on, Your Majesty.
(Blaze's mom) Thanks, babe!
(door closes)
(Snappy laughs)
- Holy cow! Wow!
- That was so cool! (squeals)
- I was a spy! What?
- Yeah, you were!
- You were the best spy!
- Wow.
(both chuckling)
- Smarty?
- (sobbing)
That was so beautiful.
That, my friend, was playin'.
- Oh, boy, did we.
- I feel so alive!
Is that what being a toy is like, Sheriff?
Well, yeah, it's… Wait, hold up.
You never called me
sheriff before in a nice way.
But, well, now I get it.
Blaze really is perfect for Bonnie.
Playing with her feels just the same.
- Your kid plays like that too?
- (chimes)
(all gasp)
- (Jessie gasps)
- (gasps) It's her!
She saw the post! It's Bonnie!
- Go on! Do it.
- Text her back.
- Go on.
(all chanting)
Text her back! Text her back.
Okay, okay, how do I do that?
(tablet beeping)
(beeping)
- (sighs)
- What? Oh, yes!
- All right!
- She's coming.
- Bonnie's coming here.
- (Snappy) I knew she would.
Blaze and Bonnie are gonna meet.
- (beeping)
- Smarty, what are you typing?
- Delete that right now.
- What?
I'm just trying to get some
batteries out of the deal.
So, what's going on?
Slink, talk to me.
Hard to hear. A lot of commotion.
I bet they're arguing over
getting rid of us.
(exclaims) Are we getting donated?
- Mmm. Doughnuts.
- No, sweetie. Donated.
Wow. I love her,
but this is gonna be hard.
Shh! Quiet! I hear something.
Like tiny footsteps.
- Aw. Kind of cute.
- (footsteps approaching)
(shouting)
- Look out!
- Bonnie's coming!
Come on, Mom.
(Woody) Oh, no, Lily's going too.
(Bonnie's mom) Hold on,
Bonnie. I'm sure your toys
aren't going to run off on their own.
All right, Buzz, you've gotta stay here.
- I'm going with them.
- Why? Why just you?
Look, I just have more
field experience than you.
That is all.
You don't think I can do it.
No, I just think I can do it a little bit…
- (car engine starts)
- …better.
(gasps) You don't deserve this.
- Buzz, come on. I was only--
- Jessie put me in charge.
Which is why you should
stay here and watch the room.
There is no room without Jessie.
Buzz, no! (groans)
(♪ dramatic music playing)
(panting, grunting)
(breathing heavily)
(grunts)
Nice poncho. (scoffs)
It's good to see them fighting again.
(Slinky Dog) It sure is.
How did your toys get
all the way out here?
(grunts)
(tablet chirps)
(gasps)
Oh, how 'bout this one?
Ah, look at those puppies.
I'm saving that one.
Yeah, they came with the
latest update this morning.
I know. It never gets old.
(chuckling) She's here.
Careful, Snappy. Dad might see you.
No way. He'll be showing off
those new backgrounds forever.
(gasps) That's her! That's Bonnie!
- Bullseye, she's really here!
- (blusters)
Bonnie, come on, let's go.
(coughs) Buzz, listen. I really just…
(Woody groans)
(Atlas) Aw. (chuckles)
It was nothing. It was nothing.
Thanks, fellas.
Pretty glad I met you devices.
Ah, don't be dumping us
something you can't flush.
- (doorbell rings)
- (gasps) It's her!
Hello. Can I help you?
Hi. I'm so sorry to bother you,
but we got this message
from your daughter.
She seems to have found
my daughter's toys.
- Are they in there?
- (Blaze's mom) Oh, okay.
I'll have her get 'em.
- Blaze! Honey?
- (Blaze) Yeah?
Can you bring down
those two rag dolls you found?
- Their owner's here.
- (Blaze) Okay!
- That's our cue.
- (footsteps approaching)
(gasps)
Blaze, this is, uh…
(Bonnie's mom) This is Bonnie.
(Blaze's mom) Hello, Bonnie.
Hi. Are these your toys?
I don't play with toys anymore.
It's just they're antiques.
They do look pretty old.
Must be worth something at least, right?
No, they're not.
You should keep 'em.
(both gasp)
- (gasps)
- Oh, no.
Bonnie, you don't want them?
(stammers) Are you sure? Bonnie? Bonnie?
I don't know what's come over her.
I'm so sorry to have bothered you.
It's all right.
If you ever change your mind,
Bonnie, just let me know.
(♪ mournful music playing)
(door closes)
I don't get it. What just happened?
What is going on, Bonnie?
Okay, I guess we're going.
- (sniffles)
- (car door opens, closes)
(all gasp, grunt)
(footsteps approaching)
(door creaks)
(gasps)
Come on, Bullseye! Quick!
Before they drive away!
(grunting)
It's… It's too late for me,
Bullseye, but maybe not for you.
- Please, not for you.
- (blusters)
(grunts, breathing heavily)
- (whinnies)
- (Jessie sighs)
- Sheriff?
- Jessie? A-Are you okay?
W-What just happened?
She ditched you, Jessie.
Because of you!
Because of all you darn devices
making kids act older.
You stole all our time.
I wanted to make a difference.
I needed to make a difference.
And you ruined it.
- Ow.
- (gasps)
- Smarty, you okay?
- I'm-I'm sorry.
- Are you hurt? Did you crack?
- I'm fine. I'm fine. (sighs)
For a rag doll, you throw
quite a punch, cowgir…
Cowgirl?
- (devices gasp)
- (Bullseye whinnies)
(Snappy) Jessie?
(whistles)
Uh, Sheriff?
I'm sorry, Smarty.
It's not you.
I'm the one that's useless.
- (devices gasp)
- (blusters)
(whinnies)
(gasps) Bullseye!
Poor Jessie. Gotta find a way in.
Buzz. Buzz, where are you going?
Let's talk about this. (groans)
- (electronic wailing)
- Huh?
Uh, what… what is going on?
- State your name.
- (Woody) Whoa, whoa.
- And your purpose.
- Hey, guys. (stammers)
- Take him in.
- Guys! Whoa!
(groaning)
- Wait, wait. What's going on?
- (Jimmy Dean snorting)
(screams) My poncho!
Quiet, assassin!
(grunts) Assassin? No, I can't…
(straining)
- Buzz?
- (all gasp)
How do you know who we are? Who sent you?
(Woody) Oh, geez! What… I…
- Talk!
- (screams)
- (snorting)
- Talk about what?
- What am I supposed to know?
- You bear a holster.
You were positioned outside
our leader's stronghold.
You are an agent of Zurg!
Zurg? No! Hey!
I don't even know who your leader is!
Liar! You wish to harm
the red-haired maiden
who bears the mark of Star Command.
- Jessie.
- (Woody) No.
- Wait!
- (Woody grunting)
He is not an agent of Zurg.
(all muttering)
Well, then, who's this old man?
(stammers) Why do people keep saying that?
I'm not that old!
This old man is a toy.
Hmm. A toy?
Yes. We are all toys!
- Toy…
- (clamoring)
Our mission on this planet is
to make a child happy.
I've been dreaming about that.
You know what I mean?
- (Buzz) To play!
- To play. Play.
Hey! Buzz, can you help me…
(muffled) …get out
of the mouth of this pig?
Search your feelings, Buzz.
You know it to be true!
- (Woody groaning)
- (clamoring)
And the red-haired maiden
you seek is our toy leader.
Her name is Sheriff Jessie.
(all) Sheriff Jessie.
Sheriff Jessie is trapped
inside that stronghold.
We must infiltrate it and rescue her
and her trusty steed.
How do you know all this?
Because I am her deputy.
(♪ triumphant music playing)
(all) Star Command.
Then this old man is a toy?
(muffled) This pig has bad breath!
Oh, yeah, him.
He's my sidekick. You can untie him.
And by the way, everybody,
Zurg is our dad.
- (all) No! No! (sobbing)
- Yeah.
(♪ adventurous music playing)
Hey. What's on your mind?
(Blaze) I don't know.
I just hope that girl's okay.
(Blaze's mom) Aw. She'll be fine, sweetie.
- Don't you worry.
- (door opens)
Hey, guys! Is anyone hungry?
- (Blaze) Me, me!
- (Blaze's mom) Starving!
(Blaze) Can we get Pasta Prairie, Baba?
(Blaze's dad) Ooh, I like
the way you think, anushikes.
- (panting)
- Spread out.
Not here.
Definitely not here.
Blast! Where could she be?
Commander! We found
these electronic devices.
Hey, Micro-Chippendales!
Hands off. (groans)
- (chimes)
- Whoa!
I'm getting a major signal
from all you dudes.
- I've got full bars.
- Me too. I can map for miles!
These guys are their own hot spot.
(beeping)
Oh, no. They're one of them.
They're one of us! Nice.
Hey, uh, this one's broken, by the way.
Where are you hiding Jessie, you machine?
Hey, hey. Easy there.
- Yeah!
- We're Jessie's friends!
And I have a name. It's Smarty Pants.
Hygiene instructor.
He'll wipe your--
This is serious, Mr. Pants.
It is my sworn duty as a Space Ranger--
- Ha, ha, you said "doody."
- Why, you!
Clearly, we're all friends with Jessie,
so can you just tell us where she is?
She went to the tire-swing hill!
It's at the far end of the ranch.
Gonna take me forever to waddle there.
Well, we'll need a way to get there.
(Buzz Lightyears) Commander Lightyear.
(♪ uplifting music playing)
- (gasps)
- Oh, my.
Whoa.
Bonnie? Did something happen
with your friends?
Can you show me?
You're not in trouble, Bonnie. I promise.
Oh, sweetie.
You know that you can always
talk with me and Dad, right?
About anything.
Because we love you, Bonnie, so much.
I wouldn't change
a single thing about you.
And I think a real friend
would feel the same.
Don't you?
But how about we take a break
from the group chat for now. Okay?
Let's get some ice cream.
(sobs)
Trust me, you're gonna love it.
(chuckling)
- Cool! (chuckling)
- Sure.
(chuckling continues)
Bonnie, they don't have chocolate chip.
Come pick another flavor.
(grunting)
(panting)
- (door closes)
- (engine starts)
- Mom, where's Lilypad?
- (Lilypad panting)
I'm sorry, Bonnie.
(creaks)
(sighs)
- (♪ suspenseful music plays)
- (grass rustling)
- (blusters)
- What is it?
- (♪ triumphant music plays)
- (nickers)
- (shouts)
- (music ends)
(grunts) Bullseye.
You shouldn't have followed me.
- (nickers)
- Oh, bad horse.
(blusters)
(sighs)
You go back to Blaze's,
Bullseye. You're better off.
- (♪ somber music plays)
- (whinnies, blusters)
I'm serious. She'll take good care of you.
And all those horses…
(blusters)
(whinnies)
(sighs) Bullseye, no.
I'm not going with you.
I…
can't do this again.
I can't…
love another kid
just to find out I never mattered.
I…
I can't.
(blusters)
(♪ uplifting music plays)
- (blusters)
- I didn't write that.
It must have been…
(gasps)
Emily?
(Jessie whistles)
- Daffodil, dig.
- (whinnies)
(blusters)
(music continues)
(lock clicks)
(♪ melancholy music plays)
Wait.
This ain't stuff from Emily.
It…
It's newer.
It doesn't make any sense.
She wouldn't have any of this stuff.
She'd be…
all grown-up.
(♪ uplifting music plays)
Wait.
Emily named her daughter…
after me.
Really?
(blusters)
(nickers)
(music continues)
- (grass rustling)
- (blusters)
- (whinnies)
- (♪ dramatic music plays)
Uh…
(screams) Whoa!
(groans)
(breathing heavily)
Jessie? Bullseye!
- Hey, I found 'em!
- (♪ triumphant music plays)
Woody?
- Buzz!
- Jessie!
(grunts)
You're okay.
What… What are you doing here?
We came for you, Jessie.
For me?
We all did.
Well, howdy-do, Sheriff?
We come bearing Buzzes.
Looks like 50 to me,
but I can only count to two.
(gasps)
Star Command. Star Command.
Star Command. Star Command. Star Command.
Star Command.
All right, all right, calm down.
Give her some room, fellas.
- Uh, Buzz.
- Yes?
Hey, hey, she meant that for me. Just me.
- We saw Bonnie give you away.
- You did?
It doesn't make any sense.
You're not useless, Sheriff!
- We love you!
- So much!
(Atlas sobbing)
(♪ melancholy music plays)
Look, I'm okay.
Bonnie's growing up.
And we don't get to decide
when and how that happens.
All that matters is
we were there at the right time
to help her along.
(blusters)
And I gotta believe we were.
You make us proud to be toys, Jessie.
- What are you doing? Stop!
- (groaning)
(clears throat) Sorry, guys. Sorry.
(blusters)
Just wish she had at least
connected with Blaze.
Wait.
- Connect! They still can!
- (♪ upbeat music plays)
Lilypad can do that!
- Lilypad?
- (grunts)
- (beeps)
Okay, okay. Guys, message coming through.
"Jessie, I'm so sorry.
Chose wrong friends. Hurt Bonnie."
- Oh, no.
- Bonnie.
Smarty, send a reply. "You can fix it."
- (beeps)
- (gasps)
"No, I can't. Threw myself away."
- What?
- "On donation truck."
Jumpin' Jehoshaphat!
Now she throws herself away?
(groans) We're goin' after her.
- What?
- But how?
Smarty, tell Lily to send
a photo of where she is.
Got it.
Snappy, zoom in on that blurry road sign.
Look at you with that tech talk, cowgirl.
Martin Avenue.
Atlas, can you get us to that truck?
Already mapped it, cowboy lady.
Tell Lily to keep sending
photos of where she is.
We're getting her back.
Yes, Sheriff.
Jessie, when you have a moment,
there's something you'd like to ask me…
- I'd like to ask you.
- Sure thing, Deputy.
- Now, a little help?
- Yes, Sheriff.
Yeehaw!
Let's ride.
(♪ triumphant music plays)
Whoa! Hey!
- Hey! Hey, wait for us!
- Hey! Wait for us!
(screams)
- (squeaking)
- (grunts)
(grunts)
(breathing heavily)
(beeps)
- (music continues)
- She's not far.
If we go south five blocks,
then east for two,
we might be able to head 'em off
before they reach the highway.
Car!
(music stops)
- Clear!
- (music resumes)
She just passed a gas station.
(laughs) Passed gas. Sorry, had to.
We're close. Take a shortcut.
Down this next road to the right.
- (squeaks)
- (grunts)
It's a house!
I don't get it. There should be a road.
Probably was a road
five years ago. Old map.
- Recalculating.
- No time. We're going through.
- (Buzz) Wait, what?
- (Woody) Going through?
(music continues)
(Smarty) Down, boy, down!
(Woody screams)
- (screams)
- (Buzz) Whoa, whoa.
- (Woody grunts)
- (dog barks)
(barking)
- Yeehaw!
- (screams)
- (chicken squawks)
- (Jessie screams)
(squawking)
(music continues)
(coughs)
(chuckles)
(shutter clicks)
The truck. I see it up ahead.
- (beeping)
- (♪ dramatic music plays)
Follow me.
(Buzzes) Yes, Sheriff.
- (screams)
- (squeaks)
(Atlas) Whoo!
We have reached our destination.
- Lily?
- Lily!
- Lily, where are ya?
- (Smarty) Lily!
- (Jessie) Lily?
- Lilypad, where you at?
Hey, Lily.
Yes, can I help you?
Lily. It's okay. We got ya.
You shouldn't have come, Jessie.
Nuh-uh. No time for pity parties, Lily.
Bonnie still needs you to make a friend.
Me? But I…
I made a major miscalculation
with Kara, Chelsea and Heidi.
You were right. Bonnie's different.
She deserves better.
Lily.
You didn't know those girls
were wrong for Bonnie.
No, I'm wrong for Bonnie.
- I'm the one who caused this.
- Well, then help me fix it.
I found Bonnie the right friend.
- You did?
- Yep.
So, how about you and me connect them?
Uh… Okay.
But first, we gotta get
everyone off this truck
and back home.
(screaming)
(music continues)
- (horn honks)
- (grunts)
Uh, we are moving way too fast
to get off now.
And we're going farther away
by the second.
There's gotta be something we can do.
We've got all these fancy Buzzes.
(gasps)
Excuse me. Move, move. Out of the way.
Spaceman, turn around.
- Snap!
- (gasps) Yes, yes, yes, yes!
No way.
Oh, yeah. Way.
(♪ triumphant music plays)
Ready, Sheriff?
Punch it, Lily.
(electrical humming)
(radio beeps)
(whirring)
Whoa.
Fly. Be free!
Show-offs!
(laughs) Wow.
Whoo-hoo!
- Whoo!
(laughs)
Now, this is flying.
With style!
Yeehaw!
So, we're clear on the plan?
Once you're at Bonnie's,
you send the message.
Blaze brings me and Bullseye to the house,
and this time, they connect!
Jessie, wait.
What if Bonnie rejects you again?
If they become friends, it's all worth it.
Yes, Sheriff.
Huh? Wait. Jessie, wait!
What?
What is it, Buzz?
Just listen to me.
I… I've been trying
to ask you this, and if…
if I don't do it now, I never will.
- (♪ romantic music plays)
- Will you…
Buzz, you can do this.
Will… Will…
(gasps)
You're stuck with me, Deputy.
Cheer up, boys. She'll be back.
We have a plan!
At ease, Ranger. At ease.
(music ends)
(♪ somber music plays)
(whirring)
Men, you know your mission.
Yes, Commander.
(♪ suspenseful music plays)
Woody! Buzz!
- What?
- (Rex) Lily!
- Oh, no, no, no.
- Foul device.
What's she doing here?
She's one of us, guys. Deal with it.
Listen up, everyone.
Lily and Jessie
have a plan to help Bonnie.
Okay, what do you need us to do?
Nothing.
- Nothing?
- That's easy.
Jessie already did the hard work.
Classic Jessica.
All that's left for me
is to send a message.
(whirring)
(♪ happy music plays)
(grunts)
It's up to the girls now.
(yawns)
(music continues)
(gasps)
(giggles)
Hey, sweetie.
Look what I found in the car.
(gasps)
It's okay. We turned off the chat.
(♪ somber music plays)
(doorbell rings)
Bonnie. You have a friend at the door.
(gasps)
- Let's try to beat…
- Hi, Bonnie.
- …our high score.
- I brought your dolls.
Bonnie, come say hi.
Okay.
Hi.
I'm sorry. I don't play with toys--
I played with her a little yesterday.
I like it when she's like,
"I ain't afraid of nothin', partner."
(chuckles)
That… That was weird.
Uh… I…
Sorry I bothered you.
- Oh, no. Don't go.
- No, no, no.
- She can't go. She can't go.
- No, no, no, no.
Blaze!
I like your boots.
I… I really like your socks.
Do you like my beard, madame?
Very impressive, m'lady.
Yes, I'm one billion years old.
That's why it's so glorious.
(Bonnie and Blaze laughing)
Um…
Do you wanna play?
(gasps)
Okay.
- Walter, let's go.
- Okay. Okay.
- Do you actually have a horse?
- Yeah.
(Bonnie) Like, a real one?
(Blaze laughs) Yes! It's real.
(gasps) Hey, I have an idea.
(♪ ceremonial music plays)
(chattering)
- (door opens)
- (gasping)
(gasping, clamoring)
(Dolly) Look at that kilt.
(gasps)
(blusters, cries)
(sniffling)
Please, take care of my son.
(clears throat)
Friends, we are gathered here today
to witness the most wonderfulest union
of Sheriff Jessie
and Buzz-tholomew MacLightyear.
- (creaks)
- (beeping)
Now, Sheriff,
please put this ring
onto Buzz's itty-bitty finger
and make your vows.
Buzz, will you take this ring
as my pinky promise
to have fun, and play with you and stuff,
for all my days,
even the hard ones?
- I do--
- (Bonnie's mom) Bonnie…
have you seen my wedding ring?
- (gasps)
- (giggles)
- (shushes) Uh…
Maybe check the bathroom?
Wait, wait, wait. We need, like…
Flowers! From the garden.
- Good idea.
- Follow me.
And there's confetti in the craft drawer.
Oh, congrats, you two.
Don't worry. I took plenty of photos
for Smarty and the gang.
That's really sweet of you, Lily.
(chuckles)
Mmm.
You done good, Sheriff.
You can call me Jessica.
Okay, I will. Jessica.
Actually, no. No.
Okay.
(beeping)
Hey, when you get a chance,
can you introduce me to the ring bearer?
- Oh.
- Awooga.
Okay.
(gasps) They're coming.
I got it. That's awesome.
That's such a good idea.
The wedding is on.
Okay!
- (Bonnie) Buzz…
- Buzz,
do you take me as
your super cool, sheriff wife?
I do.
And do you take me as your handsome,
Space Ranger husband?
- Oh.
- (gasps)
I do.
Then I now pronounce you--
I object!
Oh, no.
Buzz is already married…
to me!
(♪ dramatic music plays)
(gasping)
This is the third time
this has happened to me!
How could you?
Slap.
(groans) Jessie, it's not what you think.
Tell them, Buzz! Tell them about our love!
But, Trixie, that was then…
…and this is now.
(Bonnie) Protect the babies!
You'll hear from my lawyers about this!
- This is an outrage.
- Tell them, Buzz.
- Congratulations.
- You got this, Deputy.
- So did you help?
- Yeah.
We just followed Jessie's lead.
- Woody, will you…
- Um…
- …hold these? I'll drive.
- Well… (chuckles)
Ooh, la la.
(grunting)
- Yes! Oh, look at them.
- They're glowing.
They're such good friends.
Okay, save that one.
- Fierce.
- Oh, my gosh. Yes!
Okay, Buzz with the kilt.
(Bonnie) I'm moving to Palm Springs.
(Blaze) What if Trixie
poisoned the wedding cake?
- (Bonnie) But, Trixie, why?
- (cackling)
Hey, would you ever wanna sleep over?
(gasps) Yes! That'd be so fun.
Look. Look, look.
Friends forever, partner.
(Blaze) Come on, Jessie.
We'll take my spaceship.
- Where to first?
- Neptune!
What are you guys doing?
Honeymooning!
Wanna come?
- Sure!
- Wait, wait.
Look, Jessie, space dolphins!
Hi, dolphin.
(♪ happy music playing)
(♪ "I Knew It, I Knew You" plays)
(Taylor Swift) ♪ I knew you ♪
♪ Through the daze
Of the blades of the grass ♪
♪ In summer ♪
♪ Parachutes ♪
♪ For the free fall
Of being younger ♪
♪ I memorized the sound
Of your bare footsteps ♪
♪ Running wild ♪
♪ It's been a long time ♪
♪ Life has ways
Of leaving those days behind ♪
♪ But seeing you tonight ♪
♪ I remembered I loved you ♪
♪ Came back when it mattered
I saw you ♪
♪ Standing there
In the light of the window ♪
♪ Wearing that same smile ♪
♪ Man, it's been a while ♪
♪ But I knew it, I knew you ♪
♪ I knew it, I knew you ♪
♪ I knew you ♪
♪ All your blues ♪
♪ Like a mood ring
Changing colors ♪
♪ You did too ♪
♪ There were times
We could fight like brothers ♪
♪ I watched you drive
Around the bend ♪
♪ For what
I thought would be ♪
♪ The last time
I saw my friend ♪
♪ But love has ways
Of bringing things back ♪
♪ To life ♪
♪ All you said was hi ♪
♪ And I remembered
I loved you ♪
♪ Came back when it mattered
I saw you ♪
♪ Standing there
In the light of the window ♪
♪ Wearing that same smile ♪
♪ Man, it's been a while ♪
♪ But I knew it, I knew you ♪
♪ I knew ♪
- ♪ I knew, I knew ♪
- ♪ I knew it, I knew you ♪
♪ Oh the rivers I cried ♪
♪ When we said goodbye ♪
♪ Wondering if I'd made it up
In my mind ♪
♪ And now you looked me
In the eye ♪
♪ And you told me
I loved you ♪
♪ Came back when it mattered
I saw you ♪
♪ Standing there
In the light of the window ♪
♪ Wearing that same smile ♪
♪ Yeah, it's been a while ♪
♪ Man, it's been a while ♪
♪ Been a while ♪
♪ Wearing that same smile ♪
♪ Man, it's been a while ♪
♪ But I knew it, I knew you ♪
♪ I knew you ♪
- ♪ I knew ♪
- ♪ I knew it, I knew you ♪
♪ I knew you ♪
♪ Wearing that same smile ♪
♪ I knew it, I knew you ♪
♪ I knew it! ♪
(chattering)
(♪ somber music plays)
(laughing, chattering)
Whoa!
(whirring)
Huh?
(gasps)
I am Buzz Lightyear.
To infinity and beyond!
(gasps)
(children cheering)
(children laughing)
Hey! You kids play nice. I--
Oh.
(laughing)
Mission accomplished.
(beeping)
(cackling)
We meet again, my son.
(Buzzes) No!
- I don't know how to do this.
- Drop the beat.
- ♪ Hey ♪
- ♪ Me and the toys ♪
- ♪ Make a friend ♪
- ♪ Toys ♪
- I can't do this.
♪ Try to get Bonnie
To make a friend ♪
- ♪ All summer ♪
♪ Me and the toys
Been workin' ♪
- ♪ Been workin' all summer! ♪
- ♪ Make a friend ♪
- (toy A) ♪ Hey, yeah ♪
What does it even mean?
♪ Hey, hey
Me and the toys ♪
♪ Me and the toys been
Workin' all summer ♪
♪ Try to get Bonnie
To make a friend ♪
- ♪ Toys ♪
- ♪ Make a friend ♪
(toy F) ♪ All summer ♪
(Mrs. Potato Head) It needs a melody.
Make it stop.
Pizza con gafas, baby.
(Smarty Pants) I am not a chair!